Lois Gibbs Love Canal Papers MS063
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, circa 1951 -- 2007; MS063.001; 19.2 Linear Feet 16 record cartons
  - Environmental Support Center correspondence, circa 1999 -- 2001; MS063.001.013.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Environmental Support Center correspondence and financial records, 1998 -- 1999; MS063.001.014.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Environmental Support Center's capacity building initiative tools, circa 2000 -- 2001; MS063.001.014.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Salaries and compensation, 1999 -- 2000; MS063.001.014.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Support Center memorandums and financial records, 2001 -- 2002; MS063.001.014.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lois Gibbs correspondence with enclosed photographs, 1990; MS063.001.014.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - LEAF Board of Directors manual, 2003; MS063.001.014.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - LEAF vision statement and minutes, circa 2005; MS063.001.014.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - LEAF financial records and revitalization plan, circa 2004 -- 2007; MS063.001.014.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - LEAF board of director minutes, circa 2005 -- 2006; MS063.001.014.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hooker Chemical Corporation house organs, circa 1956 -- 1975; MS063.001.014.00010; 2 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund survey data and correspondence, circa 1986; MS063.001.014.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund bank statements, circa 1985 -- 1988; MS063.001.014.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - "Love Canal Medical Trust Fund Medical Benefit Plan", 1994; MS063.001.014.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund minutes, circa 1991 -- 2007; MS063.001.014.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund minutes and correspondence, circa 1995; MS063.001.014.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund financial statements and minutes, 1991 -- 2007; MS063.001.014.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence, circa 1995; MS063.001.014.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund minutes, circa 1997 -- 2001; MS063.001.014.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and notes, circa 1993; MS063.001.014.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund notes, circa 1994; MS063.001.014.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper clipping about birth-related medical costs, 1994; MS063.001.014.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund financial statements and minutes, circa 1992 -- 1993; MS063.001.014.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence, circa 1979, 1993 -- 1995; MS063.001.014.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund annual reports and financial statements, circa 1993 -- 1994; MS063.001.014.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund request correspondence, 1998; MS063.001.015.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund financial statements, 1999; MS063.001.015.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund financial statements and correspondence, circa 1993 -- 1994; MS063.001.015.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Love Canal Medical fund board of directors meeting agenda, 1992; MS063.001.015.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund financial statements and minutes, circa 1994; MS063.001.015.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and financial statements, 1994; MS063.001.015.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Changes Med. Ben. Plan. Dec. '95, circa 1985, 1996; MS063.001.015.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund financial statements, circa 1994 -- 1996; MS063.001.015.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and minutes, 1994 -- 1995; MS063.001.015.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence, 1995 -- 1996; MS063.001.015.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and financial statements, 1996; MS063.001.015.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund benefit plan revisions, 1998; MS063.001.015.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund minutes and financial statements, 1998 -- 1999; MS063.001.015.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund minutes and financial records, 1999 -- 2000; MS063.001.015.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund benefit plans and correspondence, 1999; MS063.001.015.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund minutes and correspondence, 1998 -- 1999; MS063.001.015.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund minutes, 1998; MS063.001.015.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund financial statements, 1996 -- 2003; MS063.001.015.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund and the Love Canal follow-up health study data and minutes, 1999 -- 2000; MS063.001.015.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund annual reports and financial statements, 2000 -- 2001; MS063.001.015.00020; 3 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 20-22)
  - Love Canal and Hooker Chemical Corporation, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.015.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Monitoring well data, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.015.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - BEV sample data, circa 1978; MS063.001.015.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Risk estimates, circa 1979; MS063.001.015.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Air data, circa 1978; MS063.001.015.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Sump data, circa 1978; MS063.001.015.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Soil data, 1964 -- 1979; MS063.001.015.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Water data and sediments, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.015.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Daily log, circa 1979; MS063.001.015.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Health questionnaire, circa 1978; MS063.001.015.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Health copies, circa 1978; MS063.001.015.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Privet hedges, circa 1979; MS063.001.015.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Liver data, circa 1979; MS063.001.015.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Census data/population, circa 1970 -- 1980; MS063.001.016.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Safety numbers, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Repairs, circa 1979; MS063.001.016.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Storm sewers, 1968 -- 1974; MS063.001.016.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - LCHA, circa 1979; MS063.001.016.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Geophysical survey, circa 1978; MS063.001.016.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Migration, circa 1978; MS063.001.016.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Groundwater, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, circa 1979; MS063.001.016.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - On site reports, circa 1979; MS063.001.016.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Maps, circa 1979; MS063.001.016.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Leachate treatment, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.016.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - TCDD, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Chemicals identified, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Construction plans, circa 1979; MS063.001.016.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Notes and statements, circa 1970 -- 1980; MS063.001.016.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Love Canal press, 1980; MS063.001.016.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Love Canal report, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Love Canal, Levine, 1979; MS063.001.016.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Love Canal, Hooker, 1953 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - McDougall, 1979; MS063.001.016.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Love Canal: CDM, 1979; MS063.001.016.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Love Canal: Ebert, 1964 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Love Canal: RAPP, 1979; MS063.001.016.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Love Canal: J. Sherman, 1979; MS063.001.016.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Love Canal: Kim, 1980; MS063.001.016.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Love Canal: Huffaker, 1979; MS063.001.016.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Love Canal: D. Owens, 1979; MS063.001.016.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Love Canal: Axelrod, 1978; MS063.001.016.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Love Canal: Vianna, 1980; MS063.001.016.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Love Canal: Slack, 1980; MS063.001.016.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Love Canal: Lester, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.016.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Love Canal: time bomb #2, 1979; MS063.001.016.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Love Canal: HEW, 1979; MS063.001.016.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Love Canal: Department of Environmental Conservation (DEC) memos, 1979; MS063.001.016.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Love Canal: climatogical survey of Niagara Falls, NY, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.016.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Love Canal: weather, 1979; MS063.001.016.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Love Canal: status report, 1979; MS063.001.016.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Love Canal: relocation, 1979; MS063.001.016.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Love Canal: health orders, 1979; MS063.001.016.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Love Canal: on-site health data, 1979; MS063.001.016.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Love Canal: DOH, 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.016.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Love Canal: LCHA, 1979; MS063.001.016.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Love Canal: Clement, 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.016.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Love Canal: status reports, 1978; MS063.001.016.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Love Canal: laterals, press, publications, circa 1979; MS063.001.016.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Newspaper clippings, 1976 -- 1982; MS063.002; 6.6 Linear Feet 5.5 record cartons.
  Newspaper clippings pertain to the Love Canal environmental disaster site and include excerpts from the Niagara Gazette, Buffalo-Courier Express, Buffalo-Courier Express/Niagara Edition, Buffalo Evening News, New York Times, San Gabriel Valley Tribune, and Los Angeles Times. This series documents the relocation of Love Canal residents, Love Canal health studies, clean-ups, and the development of the Love Canal Revitalization Agency.
  This series is arranged in received order, which is largely a reverse chronological order.
  This series is open for research.
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 April; MS063.002.017.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 March; MS063.002.017.00002; 5 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 2-6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 February; MS063.002.017.00003; 4 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 January; MS063.002.017.00004; 3 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 11-14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 December; MS063.002.017.00005; 2 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 November; MS063.002.017.00006; 4 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 17-20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 October; MS063.002.017.00007; 4 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 21-24)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 September; MS063.002.017.00008; 2 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 25-27)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 August; MS063.002.017.00009; 2 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 28-29)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 July; MS063.002.017.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 June; MS063.002.017.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 May; MS063.002.017.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 April; MS063.002.017.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 February; MS063.002.017.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 July; MS063.002.017.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1977; MS063.002.017.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1976; MS063.002.017.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 September; MS063.002.018.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 August; MS063.002.018.00002; 4 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 2-5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 July; MS063.002.018.00003; 2 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 June; MS063.002.018.00004; 4 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 May; MS063.002.018.00005; 4 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 12-15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 April; MS063.002.018.00006; 3 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 16-18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 September; MS063.002.019.00001; 4 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 October; MS063.002.019.00002; 6 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 5-10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 November; MS063.002.019.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 November; MS063.002.020.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 December; MS063.002.020.00002; 3 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
  - Newspaper clippings, mixed, 1979; MS063.002.020.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 January; MS063.002.020.00004; 5 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 7-11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 February; MS063.002.020.00005; 5 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 12-16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 March; MS063.002.020.00006; 4 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 17-20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 April; MS063.002.020.00007; 4 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 21-24)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 May; MS063.002.020.00008; 6 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 25-30)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 June; MS063.002.021.00001; 4 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 July; MS063.002.021.00002; 2 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 August; MS063.002.021.00003; 3 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 7-9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 September; MS063.002.021.00004; 3 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 10-12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 October; MS063.002.021.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 November; MS063.002.021.00006; 2 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 14-15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980 December; MS063.002.021.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1981; MS063.002.021.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, environmental, 1980 May -- 1980 June; MS063.002.021.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, circa 1978; MS063.002.022.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980; MS063.002.022.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.002.022.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979; MS063.002.022.00004; 2 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Newspaper clippings and petition demanding removal of Mayor Michael O'Laughlin, circa 1978 -- 1981; MS063.002.022.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980; MS063.002.022.00006; 2 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - Newspaper clippings and magazine articles, circa 1978; MS063.002.022.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1980; MS063.002.022.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, circa 1980; MS063.002.022.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982; MS063.002.022.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Health studies, circa 1978 -- 2010; MS063.003; 6.5 Linear Feet 5 record cartons and 1 document box.
  This series consists mainly of studies, correspondence, presentations, and reports. These materials provide information on the various health assessments and studies conducted on the Love Canal Superfund site and local residents. Other materials document the research of Beverly Paigen, the first person to conduct studies on Love Canal residents, the Love Canal Homeowners Association's response to some of the studies, and Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee meetings.
  - Health studies articles and correspondence, 1980 -- 1988; MS063.003.022.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Epidemiological studies correspondence and reports, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.003.022.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Blood types and test results, 1978 -- 1986; MS063.003.022.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Chromosome study correspondence, 1980 -- 1983; MS063.003.022.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Beverly Paigen articles and reports, 1979 -- 1983, 1990; MS063.003.022.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Beverly Paigen articles, memos, and reports, 1979 -- 1982; MS063.003.022.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Cancer study articles and correspondence, 1981; MS063.003.022.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Chromosome study articles and report, 1981 -- 1983; MS063.003.022.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Growth and maturation study presentation and report, 1983; MS063.003.022.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Voles study articles and reports, 1983; MS063.003.022.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - SUNY proposal, 1980; MS063.003.022.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Health studies articles, 1980 -- 1983; MS063.003.022.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Health studies articles, newsletters, and reports, 1978 -- 1984; MS063.003.022.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Theophylline clearance articles, 1979 -- 1984; MS063.003.023.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Love Canal: a chronology of events, 1981; MS063.003.023.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Health orders, 1978; MS063.003.023.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Heath studies newsclippings, 1982; MS063.003.023.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Lafalce and Monihan correspondence, 1979; MS063.003.023.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Love Canal Homeowners Association comments on environmental monitoring program, 1980 -- 1982; MS063.003.023.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Environmental monitoring program, 1980; MS063.003.023.00007; 2 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Greenfield comments, 1981; MS063.003.023.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - EPA correspondence on environmental monitoring program, 1981; MS063.003.023.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Longitudinal case study of the effects of prenatal environmental toxin exposure (dioxin), 1986; MS063.003.023.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Refractories and Electronics Division Chemical Application data, 1978; MS063.003.023.00017; 2 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
  - Love Canal health data sections one - twenty one, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.003.024.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Love Canal health data sections twenty two - thirty one A, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.003.024.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Love Canal health data sections thirty two - forty, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.003.025.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Love Canal health data sections forty one - forty seven, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.003.025.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Love Canal health data sections forty eight - sixty six, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.003.025.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Love Canal habitability decision correspondence, notes, and reports, 1985 -- 1992; MS063.003.026.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Love Canal hearing, 1982; MS063.003.026.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Review of materials provided by EPA on the analysis for organic chemicals in the EPA Love Canal monitoring study, 1982; MS063.003.026.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Love Canal hearing, 1983; MS063.003.026.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Water sampling data, circa 1978; MS063.003.026.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Love Canal study quality assurance plan, 1980; MS063.003.026.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Defense Fund reports, 1982; MS063.003.026.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Adverse pregnancy outcomes in the Love Canal area report, 1980; MS063.003.026.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Love Canal Homeowners Association comments on EPA Love monitoring program, 1982; MS063.003.026.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - New York State Department of Health correspondence, 1988 -- 1989, 1997; MS063.003.026.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, notes, and presentations, 1997 -- 1998; MS063.003.026.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, meeting agendas, and notes, 1997 -- 1998; MS063.003.026.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, 1997 -- 1998; MS063.003.026.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, memos, and notes, 1998 -- 1999; MS063.003.026.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, 2004; MS063.003.026.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Love Canal conference call correspondence, meeting agenda, and report, 2006; MS063.003.026.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Love Canal follow-up health study report, public comment draft, 2006; MS063.003.026.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Serum Love Canal indicator study correspondence, 2006; MS063.003.026.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Love Canal conference call correspondence, 2010; MS063.003.026.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Love Canal follow-up health study report draft, 2005; MS063.003.027.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Strategic value of health studies workshop, 2006; MS063.003.027.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, memos, and presentations, 1999 -- 2000; MS063.003.027.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, meeting agenda, and presentations, 2002; MS063.003.027.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee correspondence, notes, and reports, 2002; MS063.003.027.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Love Canal follow-up health study correspondence, notes, and reports, 2006 -- 2008; MS063.003.027.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Love Canal Expert Advisory Committee meeting agenda and presentations, 2006; MS063.003.027.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry Grant correspondence, 2000; MS063.003.027.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Birth defects, 2004; MS063.003.027.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Love Canal newsletter, 1997 -- 2004; MS063.003.027.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Cancer modeling of incidence using survival analysis techniques study interim report, 2002; MS063.003.027.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 11)